Jerome Kern Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-95, Box 103-116)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-94, Box 103-116)
    - Lucky (1927) by Otto Harbach, Bert Kalmar, Harry Ruby and Jerome Kern
      - Opening act II: #13, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil; 12 p.; Includes: "This is where the best people come" "The pearl of broadway" (Box-folder 23/19)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-3, a-d (Box-folder 22/10)
      - Le dernier crime de Bennette, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 22/10)
      - Pearl of Ceylon: #2, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in Kern's hand; 6 p. (Box-folder 23/20)
      - Ruby Keeler dance, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 22/11)
      - [Ruby Keeler dance], Arranger's holograph (Stephen O. Jones) full score in ink; p. 5-20; Includes music that became "Life upon the wicked stage" in Show Boat (Box-folder 22/11)
      - Ruby Keeler dance, Ms. piano sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 23/21)
      - *The same old moon, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 5-27; Music by Harry Ruby (Box-folder 22/12)
      - *The same old moon, Printed piano-vocal score; 7 p.; By Otto Harbach, Bert Kalmar and Harry Ruby (Box-folder 23/22)
      - *Shine on [harvest moon]: Keller sisters, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 4 p.; Music by Nora Bayes and Jack Norworth (Box-folder 23/1)
      - *Spring [is here], Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 23 p.; Music by Harry Ruby (Box-folder 23/2)
      - Intro - to Strawberry's dance, Ms. piano sketch in pencil; 2 p.; Uniform title: Strawberry's dance (Box-folder 23/23)
      - That little something, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 18 p. (Box-folder 23/3)
      - That little something, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, some lyric in pencil; 4 p.; Carbon of typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 23/24)
      - Dance refrain -- that little something, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 7 p.; Uniform title: That little something (Box-folder 23/4)
      - That little something: #7, Parts; Includes: "Dance refrain -- that little something" (Box-folder 24/1)
      - The treasure hunt see: Cingalese village see: Opening
      - *What's the matter with the moon, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 6 p.; Music by A.B. Sloane (Box-folder 23/5)
      - *When day is done, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 13 p.; Music by Dr. Robert Katscher (Box-folder 23/6)
      - When the bo-tree blossoms again see: Bo-tree
      - Without thinking of you, Ms. piano score in pencil; 3 p.; On front: unidentified sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 23/25)
      - [Unidentified], Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 34 (Box-folder 23/7)
      - [Unidentified], Ms. piano sketch in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 23/26)
      - Lucky selection, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink with printed piano-vocal score laid in, or used as pasteovers; 18 p.; Includes: "Opening act II" "That little something" "Cingalese girls" "When the bo-tree blossoms again" "Dancing the devil away" "'Neath the same old moon" (Box-folder 23/27)
      - Lucky selection, Arranger's holograph (Charles N. Grant) piano score in ink; 14 p.; Includes: "Opening act I/Cingalese village" "Cingalese girls" "That little something" "When the bo-tree blossoms again" "Ballet" "The same old moon" "Dancing the devil away" (Box-folder 23/28)
      - [Cello parts A-K], Parts (Box-folder 24/2)
      - [Cello parts L-Z], Parts (Box-folder 24/3)
    - The Marriage Market (1913) lyrics by M.E. Rourke
      - I've got money in the bank, Holograph piano-vocal score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 24/4)
      - A little bit of silk, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, verse only; [3] p. (Box-folder 24/5)
      - A little bit of silk, Printed piano-vocal score, refrain only; p. 5 (Box-folder 24/5)
      - A little bit of silk, Parts (Charles N. Grant arrangement) (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Men of the Sky
      - [Various titles] see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
    - Miss 1917 (1917) lyrics by P.G. Wodehouse (some lyric sheets indicate Century Show)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets, some with annotations in pencil; [16] p.; Note: On back [We want to laugh]: Song: Bessie McCoy & girls: typed page from Piccadilly Jim; Includes: [Anytime that you have troubles cutie]: Duet: Fancy Price & Willy [At a moving picture show, or, Dear old stage door]: Cigar-counter scene. Act two: scene 4 [A dancing M.D.]: Duet: White & Haig [Follow the girl]: Act I -- scene I: number to end farm scene Go, little boat: Assyrian boat-song I'm the old man in the moon [It's a great life]: Trio: Douglas Fairbanks, Charlie Chaplin and Mary Pickford [The New York girl]: Scene II: Number to end the plaza scene [Nurse, nurse, nurse]: Hospital scene Palm Beach girl song Peaches: act one, scene one The picture I want to see: act two: film city scene [The society farmerettes]: Act one, scene one [Tell me all your troubles cutie]: Duet: Brice & King: scene II [We want to laugh]: Song: Bessie McCoy & girls We're crooks (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Miss Caprice
      - [Various titles] see: Lieber Augustin
    - A Modern Eve (1915) lyrics by Harry B. Smith
      - I'd love to dance through life with you See also: Dance through life with you in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 24/8)
      - [I've just been] waiting for you, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p.; Note: this full score may have been intended for Very Good Eddie (Box-folder 24/9)
      - I've just been waiting for you, Printed piano-vocal score; 5 p.; Note in Kern's hand: "Duet. (Elsie & Dick)" [indicating usage in Very Good Eddie] (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Music in the Air (1932) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II (full scores have some water damage)
      - And love was born, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 27/7)
      - Balloon dance: #11, Parts (Box-folder 28/1)
      - Bedroom curtain: #22, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 25/1)
      - Bedroom curtain, or, Prayer act II: #22, Parts (Box-folder 28/2)
      - Egern for Lilli, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 16 p. (Box-folder 25/2)
      - Egern for Lilli: #21, Parts (Box-folder 28/3)
      - Entr'acte: #15, Parts (Box-folder 28/4)
      - Final scene, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil, annotations in pencil; 70 p. + p. 15.5 + insertions (6 p.; 8 p. lead sheet/conductor's score for "Edendorf"; and [1] p. choral score); Includes: "We belong together" (Box-folder 25/3)
      - Final scene: #27, Parts; Includes "Goat song," or, "Goat music" (Box-folder 28/5)
      - Finale ultimo, Parts (Box-folder 28/6)
      - Finale zoo scene, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 32 p. (Box-folder 25/4)
      - Finale zoo scene: #17, Parts (Box-folder 28/7)
      - Finaletto (prologue): #2, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 12 p.; At end: "Segue Boy No." (Box-folder 25/5)
      - Boy no.: #3, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; p. 6-11 (Box-folder 25/5)
      - Finaletto: #2; Interlude: #3; Opening act I: #4, Parts (Box-folder 29/1)
      - Frieda sings hurdy gurdy, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 8 p. (Box-folder 25/6)
      - Frieda's Abgang: #19, Parts (Box-folder 29/2)
      - Frieda's cue: #10, Parts (Box-folder 29/3)
      - I am so eager, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 27/8)
      - I'm alone, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p.; Note: first written for The Cat and the Fiddle (see box 4, folder 7) (Box-folder 27/9)
      - I'm coming home, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 110 p. (Box-folder 25/7)
      - I'm coming home: #13, Parts (Box-folder 29/4)
      - In Egern on the Tegern See, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 27/10)
      - Interlude see: Finaletto: #2 (box 29, folder 1)
      - Intro - pit scene: #24a; Pit scene (new): #25, Parts (Box-folder 29/5)
      - I've told every little star: office, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 17 p. (Box-folder 26/1)
      - I've told ev'ry little star, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 27/11)
      - I've told every little star: #12, Parts (Box-folder 29/6)
      - Melos A: #23, Parts (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Bummel intro: #8, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 2 p.; Uniform title: On the bummel (Box-folder 26/2)
      - On the bummel, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; p. 1-85, 100-107 + p. 12a-12s laid in [112 p. total] (Box-folder 26/2)
      - Stony brook scene: On the bummel: Walking song, Ms. piano-vocal score (various hands) in ink & pencil, some lyric in Kern's hand; various p. numberings with laid in items [28] p.; Uniform title: On the bummel (Box-folder 27/12)
      - Bummel, Copyist's ms. conductor's score/lead sheet in ink, annotations in pencil; 15 p.; On back: various cues in pencil; Uniform title: On the bummel (Box-folder 27/12)
      - One more dance, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 27/13)
      - Opening act I: #4 See also: Finaletto: #2 (box 29, folder 1), Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 26/3)
      - Opening act II: #16, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil, annotations in pencil; p. 1-17, 21-118, 90-91, 104-110 [124 p. total] (Box-folder 26/4)
      - Opening act II: #16, Parts (Box-folder 30/1)
      - Out march: #33, #28, Parts (Box-folder 30/2)
      - Pit scene; Steel ballet, Parts (Box-folder 30/3)
      - Pit scene (new) see: Intro - pit scene
      - Prayer: #7, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 27/1)
      - Prayer: #7, Parts (Box-folder 30/4)
      - Singverein, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 28 p.; By Hammerstein-Beethoven-Kern (Box-folder 27/2)
      - Singverein: #'s 5-6, Parts (Box-folder 30/5)
      - Small cues: office scene: #9, Parts (Box-folder 31/1)
      - I hear music: the song is you, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 8 p.; Uniform title: The song is you (Box-folder 27/3)
      - The song is you, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 27/14)
      - I hear music: #24, Parts; Uniform title: The song is you (Box-folder 30/6)
      - Reprise (song): I hear music: #26, Parts; Uniform title: The song is you reprise (Box-folder 30/7)
      - Tenor solo: [In Egern on the Tegern See], Parts (Box-folder 31/2)
      - Terzetto, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 34 p.; Note in Bennett's hand on p. 10: "N.B. Bell note might be played by neighboring trombonist if he doesn't charge $15 for doubling." (Box-folder 27/4)
      - Terzetto: #14, Parts (Box-folder 31/3)
      - There's a hill beyond a hill, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 27/15)
      - There's a hill beyond a hill: #8, Parts (Box-folder 31/4)
      - Vorspiel: #1, Parts (Box-folder 31/5)
      - Walk across, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 14 p. (Box-folder 27/5)
      - Walk across: scene change: #18, Parts (Box-folder 31/6)
      - When the spring is in the air, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; p. 1-10, 14-22, 24-41 (Box-folder 27/6)
      - When the spring is in the air, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 27/16)
      - When the spring is in the air: #20, Parts (Box-folder 31/7)
      - Music in the Air selection, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 18 p.; Includes: "I've told ev'ry little star" "There's a hill beyond a hill" "And love was born" "In Egern on the Tegern See" "I am so eager" "When the spring is in the air" "The song is you" (Box-folder 27/17)
      - [Scripts]: Music in the Air, Typed scripts, 2 bound copies; act I (56 p.), act II (56 p.) (Box-folder 32/1-2)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets, some with annotations in pencil or ink, multiple copies for some; [49] p.; Includes: Brook scene; And love was born Damn good time: bedroom scene Finale: [We belong together] I'm alone: office scene (Frieda sings solo) [In] Egern on the Tegern See Interlude (after school) [I've told ev'ry] little star: office scene (duet -- Karl and Sieglinde) Letter song: office scene (Bruno sings solo) Prologue (little girls sing offstage) We belong together Zoo scene; Included in Prologue (little girls sing offstage): "Little star (school scene)" "Melodies of May" "[There's a hill] beyond a hill" "Interlude" "When the spring is in the air" "We belong together" (Box-folder 32/3)
      - [Chorus books], Printed choral scores, 2 copies; 48 p.; Note: housed in a correspondence box container. (Box 115)
      - [Character part books], Typed part books, 2 copies for each character (the 1st copy usually in red & black, the 2nd a carbon); 82 books; Note: housed in a correspondence box container. (Box 115, Box 116)
    - The Night Boat (1920) lyrics by Anne Caldwell
      - A man to match my car, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 8 p.; Carbon of typed lyric sheet, annotated; [2] p.; Uniform title: Some fine day (Box-folder 33/1)
      - Some fine day, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; [2] p. (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Ninety in the Shade (1915)
      - Can't you see I mean you, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink & pencil, annotations in Kern's hand in pencil; [4] p.; Lyric by M.E. Rourke; Note: later used with rewritten lyric in Very Good Eddie, as "Isn't it great to be married" and in London production of Theodore and Company, with further altered lyric, as "All that I want is somebody to love me" (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Can't you see I mean you, Printed piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Curtain up act II: opening, Ms. full score in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 33/4)
      - I have been around a bit see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - *Just for to-night, or, Give me love, all your love!, Printed piano-vocal score; 4 p.; Music by Harry A. Tierney, lyric by Worton David (Box-folder 33/5)
      - Where's the girl for me?: bass solo, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 7 p.; Arranged for piano by Charles N. Miller; Lyric by Harry B. Smith; Note: right side ragged and frayed (Box-folder 33/6)
      - Whistling Dan See also: "Leave it to Jane" in Leave It to Jane See also: "Whistling Dan" in Series II -- Miscellaneous Music, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, lyric & title in Kern's hand; 5 p.; Lyric by Harry B. Smith; At top of t.p.: "(Lone Star)" (Box-folder 33/7)
      - [Unidentified], Holograph sketch in pencil, with name "Marjorie Blyth" at top; [1] p.; Ms. lyric sheet in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Nobody Home (1915)
      - Girls of yesterday; Buffo dance See also: "Buffo dance" in Very Good Eddie, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink, with some annotations in Kern's hand; 12 p. + p. 1a, 2a (additional scoring for trumpets and bassoons); Uniform title: Buffo dance (Box-folder 33/9)
      - Hyson dance, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano score in ink, pencil annotations in Kern's hand; 5 p. (Box-folder 33/10)
      - Hyson dance, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 33/10)
      - The magic melody, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, pencil notes & annotations in Kern's hand; 6 p.; Lyric by Schuyler Greene (Box-folder 33/11)
      - [The magic melody], Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [2] p. (incomplete); On back: ms. piano score in pencil of p. 4-5 above; [1] p. (Box-folder 33/11)
      - The magic melody, Printed piano-vocal score; 7 p.; Note: there is a note in Kern's hand on the copyist's ms. that was also engraved on the printed music: "This song is not a part of the score of 'Nobody Home.'" (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Oh, Boy! (1917) Lyrics by P.G. Wodehouse
      - [Ain't it a] grand & glorious feeling, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p.; Note: uses Very Good Eddie instrumentation (Box-folder 33/12)
      - Ain't it a grand and glorious feeling: Glorious feeling: #2, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 33/13)
      - Be a little sunbeam, Printed piano-vocal score, annotations in Kern's hand in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 33/14)
      - Finale act I: #9, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink & pencil, pencil annotations in Kern's hand; 14 p. (Box-folder 33/15)
      - Flubby Dub, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, with partial voice part sketched in pencil, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 33/16)
      - Letter song: #6, #7, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 33/17)
      - Nesting time in Flatbush: #13, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, incomplete vocal line, no lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 33/18)
      - Nesting time in Flatbush: #13, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [3] p. (Box-folder 33/18)
      - Trio -- Lou Ellen -- Judge -- George --: #12, Ms. (Frank Saddler) short score/sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Oh, daddy, please (Box-folder 33/19)
      - Opening act I, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score/sketch in pencil, no lyric; 6 p. (Box-folder 33/20)
      - Package of seeds see: Garden of girls in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - Rolled into one, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 33/21)
      - Why can't they hand it to me, Parts; Note: this song was used in Riviera Girl (Box-folder 33/22)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets, some with annotations in pencil; [25] p.; Includes: [Ain't it a grand and glorious feeling]: 2. Song: Jim and Girls: act one scene one [Be a little sunbeam]: Song: Jacky and chorus: #11 [Finale act I] [The first day of May]: Trio [Flubby Dub]: Trio: Jacky, Jim and George I was looking for a pal like you [Ku la loo] Letter song. Note: this lyric differs from that of piano-vocal score [Nesting time in Flatbush]: Duet: Jim and Jacky: #13 [Nesting time in] Flatbush [Nesting time in Flatbush]: Additional chorus "Flatbush" [Oh, daddy, please]: Trio: Lou Ellen, Judge, and George (2 copies) [A package of seeds] Ribbons and laces [That's the kind of man I'd like to be]: Song: George & girls: act one scene two. Note: 4 copies, title is not definite [Till the clouds roll by] [Words are not needed] You never knew about me (Box-folder 33/23)
    - Oh, I Say! (1913) Lyrics by Harry B. Smith
      - Katy-did, Holograph piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 33/24)
      - Katy-did, Parts (arranged by Charles N. Grant); Includes: "A wifie of your own" (Box-folder 33/25)
      - A woman's heart: act II: terzette: #4, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, some annotations in Kern's hand; 10 p. (Box-folder 33/26)
    - Oh, Lady! Lady!! (1918) Lyrics by Guy Bolton & P.G. Wodehouse
      - Before I met you, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 34/1)
      - Bill, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p.; Note: sketch & notes on back of p. 1 (Box-folder 34/2)
      - The dance I'd do, Holograph piano score in pencil, annotations by Frank Saddler; [1] p. (Box-folder 34/3)
      - Dear old prison day[s], Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil and ink, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 34/4)
      - Do it now: #3, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 34/5)
      - Do look at him see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - Finale act I: no. 8, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil (some in Kern's hand), pencilled lyric in P.G. Wodehouse's hand; 12 p. (Box-folder 34/6)
      - Finale I, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 6 p. (Box-folder 34/7)
      - Greenwich village: no. 13, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil, 2nd set of lyric in pencil in P.G. Wodehouse's hand; 4 p. (Box-folder 34/8)
      - Greenwich village, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 34/8)
      - I'm to be married today see: Opening act I see: Opening chorus
      - It's a hard, hard world [for a man], Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil and ink, no lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 34/9)
      - [Little] ships come [sailing] home, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [2] p. (Box-folder 34/10)
      - Moon song: opening act II: #9, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink with a single lyric correction in pencil in P.G. Wodehouse's hand; 4 p. (Box-folder 34/11)
      - [Moon song], Ms. sketch for introduction in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 34/12)
      - Introduction to act II: moon song, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; [1] p.; Uniform title: Moon song (Box-folder 34/12)
      - [Moon song]: #9, Ms. (Frank Saddler) sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Moon song (Box-folder 34/12)
      - Moon, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano score/piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [2] p.; Uniform title: Moon song (Box-folder 34/12)
      - Not yet: #2, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric [3] p. (Box-folder 34/13)
      - Oh lady - lady, Ms. (Max Hirschfeld) piano-vocal score in ink; [5] p. (Box-folder 34/14)
      - Opening act I: opening chorus act I: no. 1, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil in P.G. Wodehouse's hand; 10 p.; Includes: "I'm to be married today" (Box-folder 34/15)
      - Opening act II see: Moon song
      - Opening chorus - act I, Ms. (Max Hirschfeld) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil, some in Kern's hand; 5 p.; Includes: "I'm to be married today" (Box-folder 34/16)
      - Our little nest: no. 4, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 34/17)
      - Our little nest, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 34/17)
      - Our little nest: #4, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 3p. (Box-folder 34/17)
      - Overture, Ms. (Max Hirschfeld) piano score in ink, some pencil annotations in Kern's hand; 9 p. (Box-folder 34/18)
      - Some little girl, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano score/sketch in pencil; 2 p.; Note: originally "Beach duet" for Century (Box-folder 34/19)
      - Wedding scene see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - Wheatless day, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 34/20)
      - [You found me and] I found you: #7, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 34/21)
      - Oh, Lady! Lady!!, Printed piano-vocal score, includes photographs; 90 p. (Box-folder 34/22)
      - [Sketches], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: "Opening chorus: I'm to be married today" (Box-folder 34/23)
      - Oh Lady! Lady!! selection, Ms. (Charles Miller) sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 34/24)